trueswitch.com 2005-04-04

# Welcome to TrueSwitch. Support Center

Esaya, Inc. ("Esaya") has created this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to demonstrate our commitment to customer privacy. Privacy on the World Wide Web site located at [http://www.trueswitch.com/ ](http://www.trueswitch.com/)and other computer systems operated by Esaya (collectively, the “Website”), is of great importance to us. Because we gather important information from our users, we have established this Privacy Policy as a means to communicate our information gathering and dissemination practices. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy and will provide notification of the change at least thirty (30) days prior to the change taking effect.

Please be aware that the TrueSwitch Wizard, Website and Services are not intended for use by children under the age of 13. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Website nor should you sign up for the Services offered by Esaya. 

Any capitalized terms used and not defined in the Privacy Policy are defined in the Terms of Service.  

**1\. COLLECTED INFORMATION**  
We require users who sign-up to use the TrueSwitch Internet Service Provider (“ISP”) switching services ("Services") offered on our Website to provide their User ID and / or e-mail address and passwords for their old and new Internet accounts. This information is required to authenticate your access to each ISP service and e-mail account as well as to provide the Services of copying your personal data (including, stored e-mails, address books and calendar / scheduling information), and forwarding e-mails from your old e-mail account to your new e-mail account. We may need to collect additional information if you wish to utilize the account cancellation component of the Services. In such cases, we will only collect the additional information required to initiate cancellation of your old account.

  If payment is required for the Services, Esaya will request your name, mailing address, phone number, credit card information and other information to securely process the financial transaction. This billing information is not used by Esaya for marketing or promotional purposes. Esaya uses a third-party intermediary to manage the credit card processing. This intermediary is solely a link in the distribution chain, and is not permitted to store, retain, or use the information provided, except for the sole purpose of credit card processing.

  Using the Services requires the Website to temporarily host data and information ("Data") to copy your personal data and forward e-mails from your old Internet account to your new Internet account. Such Data may include forwarded e-mails, contents of your address books, number and size of messages received, the domain name and addresses of e-mail senders, and the number and size of e-mail attachments. When messages or information is retrieved from your old Internet account, it is stored in a queue for processing. Once the messages or information is sent to your new Internet account, the messages or information is deleted. Esaya does not scan the messages or information for specific words or phrases and will not read, share, distribute, print, reference or disclose to third parties private e-mail communications or other messages or Data that are transmitted using the Services excepting as required for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issue, or suspected violation of the Terms of Use, or as may be required by law.

  Esaya also collects information about your usage of various components of the Services, including the number of e-mails, address book entries, favorites and calendar entries copied to your new account, the number of Change of Address Notification and Update Contact Information Notification messages sent on your behalf and whether or not you selected E-mail forwarding and help with account cancellation. You can access this information via the My TrueSwitch section of the Website at https://www.trueswitch.com/mytrueswitch/login.jsp.

  We may also collect Website usage statistics such as Internet addresses, browser types, domain names and page requests. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, prepare for network load demands, and to administer our Website in order to constantly improve the quality of the Services.

**2\. CORRECTING/UPDATING/DELETING INFORMATION.**  
You have the right to access and correct, update, and/or delete your Information at any time. You can do so via the My TrueSwitch section of the Website accessible at https://www.trueswitch.com/mytrueswitch/login.jsp.  
Your User ID to login to My TrueSwitch is your new e-mail address and the password that you originally used for that account when you used TrueSwitch. A request to revise or edit your personally identifiable information may not be accommodated if it would result in incorrect information. Requests for deletion of certain key information, such as e-mail address, may require closing your TrueSwitch account.

**3\. COOKIES**  
When you interact with the Website we strive to make that experience easy and meaningful. When you come to our Website, our server sends a cookie to your computer. Cookies are small text files that Web browsers place on a computer's hard drive and are used to tell us whether users and visitors have visited the Website previously.

  Standing alone, cookies do not identify you personally. They merely recognize your browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself by signing-up for the Services, you remain anonymous. Cookies come in two flavors: session and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you've closed your browser or turned off your computer. They include such information as a unique identifier for your browser.

  Our Website uses session cookies containing encrypted or encoded information including your username and session ID. This information allows us to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies help us make sure you are who you say you are after you've logged in and are required in order to use the Services. Our Website also uses persistent cookies, that only our Website can read and use, to identify the fact that you are a TrueSwitch user or prior Website visitor (whatever the case may be). We are especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, we do not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies.

  Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, invisible GIFs, web bugs, or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookies on the Website. This technology tells us how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a page. We do not use this technology to access your personally identifiable information; it is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about Website usage. We may share aggregated Website statistics with partner companies but do not allow other companies to place clear gifs on the Website.

  Users who disable their Web browsers' ability to accept cookies will be able to browse the Website but may not be able to successfully use the Services.

**4\. THIRD-PARTY SITES**  
The Website contains links to other web sites. Should you click on an advertisement in an e-mail message or on the Website, the advertiser, or a company on its behalf, may collect information or set and access cookies on your machine. Esaya is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. Users and visitors will need to check the policy statement of these others web sites to understand their policies. Users and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential.  

**5\. ESAYA SENDS "CHANGE OF ADDRESS NOTICE" MESSAGES**  
As part of the Services, a standard "Change of Address Notice" containing your new e-mail address is e-mailed to the contacts listed in your address book. Including your new e-mail address in the "Change of Address Notice" message is intended to aid you in informing your contacts of your new e-mail address.

  The "Change of Address Notice" feature is enabled by default in the TrueSwitch Wizard, but can be disabled by selecting the “Custom Switching” mode, then de-selecting the "Notify Contacts" option. The "Change of Address Notice” message contents can be customized by selecting the “Custom Switching” mode, selecting the "Notify Contacts" option and then editing the message text in the window.

**6\. ESAYA SENDS "UPDATE CONTACT INFORMATION NOTIFICATION" MESSAGES**  
As part of the Services, an “Update Contact Information Notification” is e-mailed to the contacts listed in your address book. Including your contact information in the "Update Contact Information Notification" message is intended to aid you in informing your contacts of your new e-mail address and other personal contact information, plus facilitate their providing you with their own updated contact information.

  This feature is enabled by default in the “Custom Switching” option but disabled by default in the “Express Switching” option of the TrueSwitch Wizard. It can be disabled in the “Custom Switching” mode by de-selecting the "Update Your Contact Information" options. The information sent in the "Update Contact Information Notification” message can be customized by editing the text in each of the “Personal” and “Business” fields in the screen window following the selection of the "Update Your Contact Information" option.

**7\. SHARING OF INFORMATION**  
We will use your personally identifiable information only to provide the Services, notify you of technical or billing information, or inform you of changes in our service. We also use the information collected to contact users to further discuss interest in our company, the services that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. You may opt-out of receiving any such communications by selecting the “Custom Switching” mode in the TrueSwitch Wizard then by de-selecting the "Receive Updates from TrueSwitch" option. You may also opt-out of receiving any such communications at any time by e-mailing [opt-out@trueswitch.com](mailto:opt-out@trueswitch.com).

  TrueSwitch will send you e-mails relating to the status of your TrueSwitch and informing you of technical service or security issues related to the Services you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen.

  Esaya will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to anyone or any other company, excepting under the circumstances described below, excepting as required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process.

  If an ISP partner is sponsoring TrueSwitch, Esaya will disclose your User ID / e-mail address to that ISP partner. Please refer to the privacy policy of the sponsoring ISP if you have any concerns.  
Esaya also may share non-personalized, aggregate data with ISP partners who sponsor the Services, advertisers, investors and other selected business partners.

**8\. OPT-OUT POLICY**  
Esaya offers its users a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after signing-up for Services, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties, send us a request by e-mailing [opt-out@trueswitch. com](mailto:opt-out@trueswitch.com).  

**9\. SECURITY**  
The Website has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Data under our control. When the Website is accessed using Netscape Navigator, or Microsoft Internet Explorer versions 4. 0 or higher, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology protects information using both server authentication and data encryption to help ensure that Data is safe, secure, and available only to you. TrueSwitch also implements an advanced security method based on dynamic data and encoded session identifications, and hosts the Website in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other advanced technology to prevent interference or access from outside intruders. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of Data.  

**10\. ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**  
Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Website should be directed to Esaya’s Security Administrator by e-mailing such questions to [security@esaya.com](mailto:security@trueswitch.com).

|   |
